About Me

I am well-organised and hardworking, always putting the maximum into whatever I do. I have been passionate about computers and programming from a young age and have endeavoured to progress my skills at every stage. I am a fast learner and work well under pressure, and have acquired a varied skill set.

I have programming experience with Java and Python, and have learned web app development (HTML, PHP, CSS, JS w/ jQuery & AJAX) on my own initiative using Amazon Web Services. My work has also given me Java experience with Maven and Spring, as well as app developer experience with React Native and Expo.

Education

University of Glasgow - 2016 to Present

BSc Computing Science: on track for a first-class honours (**GPA 20.75/22.0**)

Awarded the Level 3 (third year) Honours Prize for highest overall grades

Straight A's in first and third year

Won first prize in the 2018 Glasgow Cyber Defence Exercise and the 2017 Morgan Stanley Hackathon challenge (and second prize in 2019)

Treasurer for GUBMS

Level 4 Elective Courses: Machine Learning, Distributed and Parallel Systems, Text as Data, Recommender Systems, Big Data, Database Systems, CVMA (Computer Vision)

Level 4 Project: Building a Federated Recommender System

Extracurricular Projects

Created a YouTube on-the-fly playlist service that allows users to create rooms, where other users can join and add videos to a queue. The queued videos will then automatically play on the host's device (max.ardeer.co.uk/playlist)

Assorted web projects undertaken to enhance my skill set hosted at: **max.ardeer.co.uk**

Other projects: **github.com/maxburton**

Work Experience

Barclays - May 2019 to September 2019 (Part Time Coder)

Worked alongside senior developers as part of the DPO team, picking up daily tasks from a shared JIRA board

Improved code quality of a legacy system, identifying and fixing several critical bugs

Managed Java servlets using Spring, Maven and Apache Tomcat instances

GoEatDirect - December 2018 to Present (Developer)

Cross-platform app developer & publisher

AWS server(s) admin

Configured WordPress websites w/ WooCommerce integration

Automated several manual tasks including menu parsing & creation

Implemented & managed push notifications

Trained 2 junior members about our workflow, software environment and tools

Nutriplotter - October 2018 to May 2019 (App Developer)

Level 3 Project, contacted after completion to continue work as sole developer

Developed cross-platform nutritional app from scratch in React Native & Expo

Database integration w/ MongoDB and Google Firebase

Features include a search system of 3000+ foods, a scoring system based on 13 macro and micro nutrients, and FaceBook integration

Three in One Dunoon - October 2015 to April 2016 (Shop Assistant)

Learned to handle customers both in person and over the phone

Time management skills from taking & making orders and balancing work with school

Experienced working as part of a team